Guide to the Apple Computer, Inc. Records M1007
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Apple Library, series 19
  - Publications: Magazines & Newsletters
    - The Internet Business Journal, 1995-1996 (Box 46)
    - Internet Business Report, 1994-1997 (Box 47)
    - The Internet Letter, 1994-1995 (Box 47)
    - Internet Week, 1995-1996 (Box 47)
    - Internet World, 1992-1997 (Box 47)
    - Mac Addict, 1997 (Box 72)
    - Mac Artist, 1992 (Box 72)
    - The Mac Authority, 1992-1997 (Box 72)
    - Mac/Chicago, 1989-1995 (Box 72)
    - Mac Home Journal, 1993-1995 (Box 47)
    - Mac Home Journal, 1995-1997 (Box 48)
    - Mac Home Journal, 1997 (Box 72)
    - The Macintosh Buyer's Guide, 1984-1990 (Box 74)
    - Macintosh Magazin (Germany), 1989 (Box 74)
    - Macintosh Magazine (Netherlands), 1994 (Box 74)
    - Macintosh Product Registry, 1990, 1996 (Box 74)
    - MacJapan (Japan), 1990-1992 (Box 72)
    - MacJapan (Japan), 1992-1995 (Box 73)
    - MacJapan - Active (Japan), 1994 (Box 73)
    - MacJapan - Bros. (Japan), 1994 (Box 73)
    - MacLife (Japan), 1989-1991 (Box 48)
    - MacLife (Japan), 1991-1994 (Box 49)
    - MacLife (Japan), 1994-1995 (Box 50)
    - MacLife (Japan), 1995-1997 (Box 51)
    - MacPower (Japan), 1990-1994 (Box 52)
    - MacPower (Japan), 1994-1996 (Box 53)
    - MacPower (Japan), 1996-1997 (Box 54)
    - [Mac Madang] (Korea), 1995-1996 (Box 54)
    - Mac Tech Journal, Fall 1990 (Box 54)
    - MacTech Magazine (formerly Mac Tutor), 1993-1994 (Box 54)
    - MacTech Magazine (formerly Mac Tutor), 1994-1997 (Box 55)
    - Mac Tutor, 1990-1992 (Box 74)
    - Mac Tutor, 1985-1989 (Box 73)
    - Mac User (England), 1988-1991 (Box 55)
    - MacWorld (Australia), 9/1997 (Box 55)
    - MacWorld (Korea), 1995-1996 (Box 55)
    - MacWorld (Korea), 1996 (Box 56)
    - Microcomputing, 8/1981 (Box 74)
    - Microcomputing Industry, 1979-1982 (Box 74)
    - Microcomputer Industry Update, 1995 (Box 74)
    - Microprocessor Report, 1987-1997 (Box 56)
    - Microsoft Networking Journal, 1991-1992 (Box 75)
    - Microsoft Systems Journal, 1990-1994 (Box 56)
    - Microsoft Systems Journal, 1994-1997 (Box 57)
    - Microsoft Works In Education, 1990 (Box 75)
    - Microsystems Journal, 1982-1984 (Box 75)
    - Mind Over Media, 10/1990 (Box 75)
    - Multimedia Computing & Presentations, 1989-1992 (Box 75)
    - Multimedia Review, 1990-1993 (Box 75)
    - Multimedia World, 1995-1996 (Box 57)
    - Multimedia Week, 1992-1997 (Box 57)
    - The New Leaders, 1995-1997 (Box 58)
    - New Media, 1991-1997 (Box 58)
    - Office Computing Report (after 2/1993, see Workgroup Computing Report), 1991-1993 (Box 75)
    - The Page, 1990-1996 (Box 79)
    - PC Computing (selected issues: v.2 no.11; v.6 no. 11), 1989-1993 (Box 58)
    - PC Letter, 1988-1996 (Box 58)
    - PC Magazine (selected issues: v. 5 no.1; v.12 no.3), 1986-1993 (Box 59)
    - PC Tech Journal, 1983-1984 (Box 75)
    - PC Tech Journal, 1985-1989 (Box 76)
    - Personal Computer World (England), 1986-1991 (Box 59)
    - Personal Computer World (England), 1991-1994 (Box 60)
    - Personal Computer World (England), 1994-1995 (Box 61)
    - Personal Computer World (England), 1995-1996 (Box 62)
    - Personal Computer World (England), 1996-1997 (Box 63)
    - Pixel, 1990-1991 (Box 77)
    - Printed Circuit Fabrication, 1981-1983 (Box 63)
    - Printed Circuit Fabrication, 1983-1994 (Box 64)
    - Printed Circuit Fabrication, 1994-1997 (Box 65)
    - Printout, 1986-1995 (Box 77)
    - Printout Annual, 1982-1985 (Box 77)
    - The Quicktime Forum, 1992-1993 (Box 77)
    - Release 1.0, 1985-1997 (Box 65)
    - The S. Klein Newsletter On Computer Graphics, 1983-1992 (Box 77)
    - Seybold Special Report, 1993-1994 (Box 65)
    - Seybold Special Report, 1994-1996 (Box 66)
    - Seybold Report On Desktop Publishing, 1994-1996 (Box 66)
    - Soft Letter, 1983-1997 (Box 66)
    - Software Digest Ratings Report, 1993-1997 (Box 78)
    - Software Digest Macintosh Ratings Report, 1988-1992 (Box 78)
    - Software Magazine, 1994-1995 (Box 66)
    - Software Magazine, 1996-1997 (Box 67)
    - Syllabus, 1989-1993 (Box 1)
    - Syllabus, August, 1989 (Box 81)
    - The Technological Horizons In Education Journal, 1993-1997 (Box 67)
    - Verbum, 1986-1991 (Box 79)
    - Virtual Reality Special Report, 1995-1996 (Box 67)
    - VR World, 1993-1995 (Box 67)
    - Wheels For The Mind, 1985-1989 (Box 79)
    - Windows Sources, 1994-1997 (Box 68)
    - Word Perfect, 1989-1990 (Box 68)
    - Word Perfect, 1991-1997 (Box 69)
    - Workgroup Computing Report, Snapshots, 1996-1997 (Box 70)
    - Workgroup Computing Report, Snapshots, 1993-1996 (Box 69)
    - World Of Macintosh Multimedia, 1993-1995 (Box 79)
  - Apple Museum
    - Advertising Slicks (Flat-box 131)
    - Advertising Slicks (Oversize-box 146)
    - AM/FM Microphone Radio (Box 114)
    - Application Software, third party, assorted (Box 136)
    - Apple IIc Stand (chrome) - in orginal packaging (Box 97)
    - Apple III Commemorative Plaque (Flat-box 110)
    - Apple Annual Report - 1985 (Box 120)
    - Apple Annual Report - 1986 (Box 120)
    - Apple Application Software, assorted (Box 136)
    - Apple Application Software, assorted - in orginial packaging (Box 136)
    - Apple Apparel (Sweatshirts and T-Shirts, short-sleeved and long-), circa 1997 (Box 91)
    - Apple Apparel (Sweatshirts, T-Shirts, hats, visors) (Box 99)
    - Apple Apparel (Sweatshirts, T-Shirts, pants, visors) (Box 100)
    - Apple Apparel (Sweatshirts, T-Shirts, pants, socks, headbands, etc.) (Box 104)
    - Apple Apparel (Sweatshirts, T-Shirts, etc.) (Box 105)
    - Apple Apparel (Sweatshirts, T-Shirts, etc.) (Box 106)
    - Apple Apparel (Sweatshirts, T-Shirts, etc.) (Box 107)
    - Apple Apparel (Sweatshirts, T-Shirts) (Box 101)
    - Apple Apparel (Sweatshirts, T-Shirts, visors) (Box 102)
    - Apple Apparel (Sweatshirts, T-Shirts, pants, etc) (Box 108)
    - Apple Apparel (Sweatshirts, T-Shirts) (Box 109)
    - Apple Apparel (T-Shirts) (Box 103)
    - Apple Apparel (T-Shirt) (Box 112)
    - Apple Banners (Flat-box 110)
    - Apple Banner (Flat-box 131)
    - Apple Bags, Plastic (Box 111)
    - Apple Bike Bag (Box 103)
    - Apple Binders, 3-Ring (vinyl) (Box 137)
    - Apple Buttons, assorted - mounted on board (Box 139)
    - Apple Buttons, Stickers, assorted memorabilia (Box 112)
    - Apple Buttons, Stickers, assorted memorabilia (Box 137)
    - Apple Coffee Cups, assorted (Box 115)
    - Apple Coffee Cups, assorted (Box 116)
    - Apple Coffee Cups, assorted (Box 137)
    - Apple Computer Monitor (Beige) w/ Stand (Box 94)
    - Apple Cowboy Hats (Box 115)
    - Apple Disc IIc Chrome Hard Drive - in original packaging (Card-box 140)
    - Apple Foam Squeeze Balls, various colors (Box 137)
    - Apple Frisbee (Box 111)
    - Apple Earthquake Preparedness Stack (sealed envelope) (Box 112)
    - Apple Keyboard Model #M0110 (Box 98)
    - Apple Keyboard Model #M0110A (Box 98)
    - Apple Mice (2) - Model # A2M415 and M0100 (packaged together) (Box 97)
    - Apple Sport Bottles (Box 137)
    - Apple Teddy Bear, 1985 (Box 103)
    - AppleWorks Software Package - unopened (Box 97)
    - Artifacts, Assorted (mouse pad, decals, calendar, etc.) (Box 112)
    - Artifacts, Assorted (conference memorabilia, etc.) (Box 139)
    - Awards/Trophies (Box 116)
    - Awards/Trophies (Box 117)
    - Banner, vinyl. "Apple Wishing Well" (Tube 142)
    - Banner, vinyl - red & green; reads "Apple"; approx. 3x12'; vertical orientation (Tube 141)
    - Banner, vinyl: "Ignite the Spirit" approx. 3x25' (Tube 143)
    - Banner, vinyl: "Ignite the Spirit" approx. 3x25' (Tube 144)
    - Baseball Caps (non-Apple) (Box 137)
    - CD-ROM: "Seybold San Francisco 96" (Box 112)
    - Cables and Power Cords, Assorted (Box 97)
    - Cassette Tape - "Apple Computer - Spindler Fable - 22/8/90" (Box 118)
    - Cassette Tape - "1990 Apple Worldwide Developers Conference" (Box 118)
    - Claris Banner (Box 112)
    - Clock, Walnut. Inscribed: "Omnes vulnerant, postrera necat. (Oversize-box 145)
    - Coffee Cup, plastic (Box 114)
    - Commemorative Plaques (Box 114)
    - Commemorative Plaques (Box 116)
    - Commemorative Plaques - "Train the Traniers, 1985" - printed on Glass (unframed) (Box 118)
    - Conference/Meeting Packets; Notepads, etc. (Box 111)
    - Conference Signage & Photos - Mounted on Foamcore backing, circa 1985-1987 (Box 119)
    - Conference Signage & Hardware Drawings - Mounted on Foamcore backing (Box 120)
    - Costume--Computer Halloween costume, made by employee; multiple parts; includes documentation (Oversize-box 147)
    - Consumer Slide Show (audio cassette) + commemorative pens (Box 111)
    - eWorld Starter Kit - includes two 3.5" floppy disks (Box 99)
    - "Develop: The Apple TEchnical Journal" vol. 2 #1 (Box 112)
    - Floppy discs - 3.5" - assorted software (Box 112)
    - Floppy discs- 3.5" - Macintosh Basics (Box 139)
    - Floppy disc - 3.5" - "7/90 - Apple Resource Directory" (Box 139)
    - Gemini DuoDock prototype; in orginal packaging (Oversize-box 146)
    - Keyboard Overlays, assorted (including blank) (Flat-box 132)
    - Lisa Glare Filter (Box 98)
    - Print Ad Documentation/Press Clippings/Display Material - Mounted on Foamcore (Flat-box 121)
    - Print Ad Documentation/Press Clippings/Display Material - mounted on foamcore (Flat-box 122)
    - Print Ad Documentation/Press Clippings/Display Material - mounted on foamcore (Flat-box 123)
    - Print Ad Documentation/Press Clippings/Display Material - mounted on foamcore (Flat-box 124)
    - Print Ad Documentation/Press Clippings/Display Material - mounted on foamcore (Flat-box 125)
    - Print Ad Documentation/Press Clippings/Display Material - mounted on foamcore (Flat-box 126)
    - Print Ad Documentation/Press Clippings/Display Material - mounted on foamcore (Flat-box 127)
    - Print Ad Documentation/Press Clippings/Display Material - mounted on foamcore (Flat-box 128)
    - Print Ad Documentation/Press Clippings/Display Material - mounted on foamcore (Flat-box 129)
    - Print Ad Documentation/Press Clippings/Display Material - mounted on foamcore (Flat-box 130)
    - Print Ad Documentation/Press Clippings/Display Material - mounted on foamcore (Flat-box 131)
    - Press Clipping (Box 112)
    - Promotional Display-"Machine of the Year", mounted on board; three pieces (broken) (Oversize-box 146)
    - Sales Kit - Apple Printers (Box 112)
    - Silicon Valley Napkin (Box 112)
    - Macintosh Chrome Compuer - includes comptuer and monitor (Box 138)
    - Macintosh Computer Housing, w/ Keyboard and Motherboard (Box 95)
    - Macintosh Hard Drive 20 M0135 (Box 98)
    - Mac Prototype Hard Drive - clear plactic housing - incluides Apple Museum documentation (Box 99)
    - MacCharlie 5 1/4" Disk Drive - includes Apple Musem checklist (Box 96)
    - Motherboards/Hardware (souvenir) (Box 116)
    - Photographs - assorted event photos (Box 114)
    - Promotional Material - Photographic effigies mounted on board (Flat-box 131)
    - Publication: "So Far: The First Ten Years of Apple" (Box 111)
    - NeXT - 0.9 Technical Documentation (Box 88)
    - Sales Presentation Kit: Apple Desktop Publishing; includes media; received in damaged housing (Oversize-box 149)
    - SNA Souvenir Goblets (2) (Box 137)
    - Toy Mouse, plush (Flat-box 110)
    - Toy Penguin, inflatable (Box 103)
    - Training Kit: Intermediate Macintosh Application Programming; includes media (Oversize-box 148)
    - Training Kit: Teaching, Learning and Technology, A Planning Guide (Oversize-box 149)
    - Training Kit: Macintosh Fundamentals Interactive Learning, ver. 2.0; includes media (Oversize-box 150)
    - Training Kit: Macintosh Fundamentals Interactive Learning, ver. 2.3; includes media (Oversize-box 150)
    - Videocassette - 3/4" - "Intermedia: A Retrospective" - Brown University (Box 111)
    - Apple-produced Laserdiscs
      - Making Connections: New Approaches to Bringing People and Information Together, 1993 (Box 156)
      - Mobile Computing and Product Intro Graphics, 1993 (Box 156)
      - Encyclopedia of Multimedia, The (Box 156)
      - Apple Vivarium 1986-1987, 1988 (Box 156)
      - Life Story: A Demonstration Prototype; includes data CD (Box 156)
      - Technologies for Enhancing Language Skills and Literacy, 1993 (Box 156)
      - Multimedia and Education, 1993 (Box 156)
      - Possibilities in Learning, 1992 (Box 156)
      - Chronicle: An Interactive Newspaper; includes floppy discs and user's guide (Box 156)
      - Encyclopdia of Multimedia, The; includes data CDs (Box 156)
      - In Business with Macintosh (Box 156)
      - Macintosh Solutions for Math and Science, 1992 (Box 157)
      - Network Administration Skills 1.0c; includes user guides and data CD, 1990 (Box 157)
      - Technology and the Evolving Classroom, 1993 (Box 157)
      - Multimedia in Language and Literacy, 1992 (Box 157)
      - Multimedia 101: Getting Started (Box 157)
      - MacWorld Success Stories (Box 157)
      - How Computers Are Changing the Way We Learn, 1992 (Box 157)
      - Teacher Access to Computer Technology, 1993 (Box 157)
      - Louvre, Vol. 3: Masterpieces of Antiquity; 1 laserdisc, 2 floppy diskettes, 1 catalog, 1989 (Oversize-box 158)
      - Louvre, Vol. 1: Painting Drawing; 1 laserdisc, 3 floppy diskettes, 1 catalog, 1989 (Oversize-box 158)
      - ABC Interactive Special Report: The Great Quakes of 89'; 1 laserdisc, 1 floppy diskette (2 copies), 1989 (Oversize-box 158)
      - National Gallery of Art; 1 laserdisc, 1 floppy diskette, 1983 (Oversize-box 158)
      - ABC Interactive News: In the Holy Land - Understanding Our World; 1 laserdisc, 4 floppy diskettes, 1 guidebook, 1989 (Oversize-box 158)
      - ABC News Interactive: Martin Luther King Jr. - Instant Replay of History; 1 laserdisc, 4 floppy diskettes, 1 guidebook, 1989 (Oversize-box 158)
      - The Saint Louis Zoo Presents: A World Alive; 1 laserdisc, 1 floppy diskette, 1990 (Oversize-box 158)
      - The Visual Almanac; 2 laserdiscs, 23 floppy diskettes, 1 CD-ROM, 1 companion guide, 1 help binder, 1989 (Oversize-box 159)
      - Regard for the Planet: 50,000 Photographs by Marc Garanger; 1 laserdisc, 1 floppy diskette, 1989 (Oversize-box 159)
      - The Creation of the Universe by Timothy Ferris; 1 laserdisc, 1991 (Oversize-box 159)
      - Cyberpunk, William Gibson; 1 laserdisc, 1992 (Oversize-box 159)
      - Fiction Interactive: Frame Up; 1 laserdisc, 1 floppy diskette, 1986 (Oversize-box 159)
    - Videocassette - VHS - "Day 3; 10/6/90; Spindler General Session and Close (Flat-box 131)
    - XYZ MiniDock - includes documentation (Box 137)
    - MacCharlie; 3 1/2 inch floppy diskette reader (Box 164)
    - Macintosh Hard Disk 20 (2); external harddrive (Box 165)
    - Apple buttons; 2 different buttons (Oversize-box 166)
    - Orion Network Systems (Apple) BETA Summer 1990 water bottles (2) (Oversize-box 166)
    - Apple logo puzzle (Oversize-box 166)
    - Commemorative Glass Plaques (2): Training the Trainers - Individual Business Promotion 1985 (Oversize-box 166)
  - Audiovisual Material
    - 1993 Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, San Jose, California, 5/10-14/1993
      - VHS videocassettes 1-30 (missing 1 & 2), 5/10-14/1993 (Box 16)
      - VHS videocassettes 31-60, 5/10-14/1993 (Box 17)
      - VHS videocassettes 62-91 (missing 61), 5/10-14/1993 (Box 18)
      - VHS videocassettes 92-95, 5/10-14/1993 (Box 19)
      - CD-Rom, 5/10-14/1993 (Box 19)
    - 1994 Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, San Jose, California
      - VHS videocassettes 4, 16, 18, 26, 44, 58, 86 (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous AV Material
      - Apple-produced VHS videocassettes (not part of circulating collection) (Box 19)
      - Apple-produced VHS videocassettes (not part of circulating collection) (Box 20)
      - audiocassettes (circulating collection) (Box 26)
      - audiocassettes (circulating collection) (Box 27)
      - audiocassettes (circulating collection) (Box 28)
      - audiocassettes (circulating collection) (Box 29)
      - audiocassettes (circulating collection) (Box 30)
      - audiocassettes (circulating collection) (Box 31)
      - audiocassettes (circulating collection) (Box 32)
      - JavaOne conference audiocassettes, 4/2-4/1997 (Box 34)
      - manuals & handbooks (circulating collection) (Box 25)
      - misc. software training packages - include CD-ROM, 3.5" floppy discs, etc., 1991-1994 (Box 90)
      - Third party-produced CD-Roms (circulating collection) (Box 24)
      - Third party-produced CD-Roms (circulating collection) (Box 25)
      - Third party-produced laserdiscs (circulating collection). Include floppy discs, manuals, user guides, etc. (Boxes 151-155)
      - Third party-produced VHS videocassettes (not part of circulating collection) (Box 20)
      - Third party-produced VHS videocassettes (not part of circulating collection) (Box 21)
      - VHS videocassettes (circulating collection) (Box 21)
      - VHS videocassettes (circulating collection) (Box 22)
      - VHS videocassettes (circulating collection) (Box 23)
      - VHS videocassettes (circulating collection) (Box 24)